{
    "subject": "resource/John_Boozman",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Fort_Smith,_Arkansas",
    "human_readable": "John Boozman was born in Fort Smith, Arkansas.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9158217906951904,
            "question": "Is John Boozman from Arkansas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8882527351379395,
            "question": "Where was John Boozman born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6589066386222839,
            "question": "Are there any famous people born in Fort Smith?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5882131457328796,
            "question": "What can you tell me about John Boozman's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.413168340921402,
            "question": "What state is Fort Smith in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3874657154083252,
            "question": "What is the population of Fort Smith, Arkansas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35000333189964294,
            "question": "Where might someone go to learn more about John Boozman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28116264939308167,
            "question": "Can you describe the geography of Fort Smith?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23521333932876587,
            "question": "What are some popular attractions in Fort Smith?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20990392565727234,
            "question": "Name a city in Arkansas."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John Boozman was born in Fort Smith, Arkansas.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3302_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular attractions in Fort Smith?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3302_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the geography of Fort Smith?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3302_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might someone go to learn more about John Boozman?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3302_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3302_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3302_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3302_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3302_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3302_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3302_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3302_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3302_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3302_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3302_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The information in the documents supports the triple.\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about John Boozman's place of birth, stating that he \"was born in Fort Smith, AR.\" This supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "John Boozman was actually born in Shreveport, Louisiana, not Fort Smith, Arkansas.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The birthplace of John Boozman is stated to be Shreveport, Louisiana (as per points 1, 2, and 5), whereas the claim states he was born in Fort Smith, Arkansas.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information states that John Boozman was born in Shreveport, Louisiana.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}